let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How can we initialize an array in C language?",
    answer: "int arr[2] = {10, 20}",
    options: [
      "int arr[2]=(10, 20)",
      "int arr(2)={10, 20}",
      "int arr[2] = {10, 20}",
      "int arr(2) = (10, 20)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the advantage of the array data structure?",
    answer: "Easier to access the elements in an array",
    options: [
      "Elements of an array cannot be sorted",
      "Index of the first element starts from 1.",
      "Easier to access the elements in an array",
      "Elements of mixed data types can be stored."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
    answer: "Push",
    options: [
      "Insert",
      "Add",
      "Push",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which data structure is mainly used for implementing the recursive algorithm?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Stack",
      "Binary tree",
      "Linked list"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The minimum number of stacks required to implement a stack is __",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "3",
      "2",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of the following principle does Queue use?",
    answer: "FIFO principle",
    options: [
      "LIFO principle",
      "FIFO principle",
      "Linear tree",
      "Ordered array"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " In the linked list implementation of queue, where will the new element be inserted?",
    answer: "At the tail position of the linked list",
    options: [
      "At the middle position of the linked list",
      "At the head position of the linked list",
      "At the tail position of the linked list",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Which data structure is the best for implementing a priority queue?",
    answer: "Heap",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Linked list",
      "Array",
      "Heap"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Which of the following is the time complexity to search an element in the linked list?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(logn)",
      "O(nlogn)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which one of the following techniques is not used in the Binary tree?",
    answer: "Randomized traversal",
    options: [
      "Randomized traversal",
      "Preorder traversal",
      "Postorder traversal",
      "Inorder traversal"
    ]
  },
];